(Woman at Door:)All right.
Sheldon, what's on your mind?
(Sheldon:)I wronged Howard,
and he won't accept my apology.
(Penny:)Oh, right, that.
(Penny:)Yes, Leonard told me.
Sorry, honey.
(Sheldon:)Penny, you face failure
on a daily basis.
(Sheldon:)How do you cope?
(Penny:)I drink.
(Sheldon:)To drinking.
(Sheldon:)Nope.
(Sheldon:)Oh, if only there were some way
(Sheldon:)to force Howard
to accept my apology
(Sheldon:)so I could escape
this miasma of guilt.
(Penny:)You know, sometimes
stuff just happens,
(Penny:)and there's nothing
you can do about it.
(Penny:)For example, Lisa Peterson
(Penny:)hasn't talked to me
since the 11th grade,
(Penny:)because no matter how
much you apologize,
(Penny:)you can't go back and
un-dry-hump someone's boyfriend.
(Page:)I see.
(Sheldon:)You're saying I'm facing
Starfleet Academy's
unwinnable command scenario:
the Kobayashi Maru.
(Penny:)Exactly.
(Penny:)Sometimes you can't win.